https://www.palmsens.com/cookie-policy/

You are using an outdated browser. Please upgrade your browser to improve your experience and security.
HomeProductsPalmSens4EmStat3EmStat3 BlueSensit SmartSensit BTMultiPalmSens4MultiEmStatEmStatMUX8-R2Compare productsAccessoriesAllCorrosion StudiesMultiplexersSensor cablesSoftwarePSTraceMultiTraceSoftware Development KitPStouchSDK for MATLABSensorsScreen printed electrodesClassical electrodesSensor ConnectionKitsSupportHardware SupportSoftware supportApplication NotesScientific publicationsSoftware downloadsVideo TutorialsWorldwide DistributionAbout usCareersContact UsT:+31(0)302459211E:info@palmsens.com Home » Cookie policyCookie policy What are cookies?Cookies are small, simple text files that are placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a web page. These cookies can help optimise your website visit. For example, they remember your preferences in order to show you only information that is of interest to you. Another advantage is that you do not have to log in or fill in the same information every time you visit a certain website.Why do we inform you about the use of cookies?As of 25 May 2018, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) applies. This means that from that date, the same privacy legislation will apply throughout the European Union (EU). This means, among other things, that certain cookies may only be placed with the explicit consent of the internet user.Google AnalyticsCookies can also be used to track visitor statistics. We use Google Analytics to gain insight into the behaviour of visitors to our website. This data provides us with insight into the surfing and visiting behaviour of our visitors and enables us to optimise our website for you where possible. The information that Google collects is made anonymous as much as possible. Your IP address is not given.Marketing CookiesWith the help of tracking cookies we can, among other things, advertise in a more targeted way and register which companies and organisations visit our website. This way we can adjust offers and approach visitors with interesting proposals. These cookies are only placed if you give permission to do so.Third party cookiesThird party cookies are used to record browsing behavior, history and user preferences. You can think of placing external advertisements through an ad network, collecting information to measure and analyze visitor behavior or the integration of social media channels and features. PalmSens places these cookies on your computer to prevent you from seeing a certain advertisement too often and to record the number of times an advertisement is displayed. These cookies are not linked to any online profile about you.Social MediaOn the website of PalmSens a pixel has been included to register and store visits by LinkedIn users in an online target group. This pixel works by means of a piece of code that originates from LinkedIn itself. Cookies are placed through this code. PalmSens has no influence on this. Please read the privacy statement of LinkedIn (which may change regularly) to read what LinkedIn does with your (personal) data through these cookies.The information that LinkedIn collects is anonymized as much as possible. This means that PalmSens can only see general characteristics of visitors and can not view personal information, properties and preferences for each visitor. The information is transferred to and stored by LinkedIn on servers in the United States. LinkedIn states to adhere to the Safe Harbor principles are affiliated with the Safe Harbor program of the U.S. Department of Commerce. This means that there is an adequate level of protection for the processing of any personal data.Accept or refuse cookiesYou can decide for yourself whether to accept or refuse cookies. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies by default, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. You will need to reset this for each browser and each computer. An explanation of how to change the settings can be found in the ‘help function’ of your browser:Google Chrome (our personal favourite)Internet ExplorerMozilla FirefoxApple SafariPlease note: Some features and services, on our and other websites, may not function properly if cookies are disabled in your browser.More information about cookies?You can find more information about cookies on the following websites:European UnionEU WikiWikipediahttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookieIs your request complete?
bg
DisclaimerCookie policyPotentiostatCookies on Palmsens.comWe use functional, marketing and tracking cookies to improve your experience on our website. More information about cookiesAccept cookiesPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non Necessary
non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website. Save & Accept Highlight Differences Compare Products Clear All Compare Now
